DANG TRUNG HIEU

WEB DEVELOPER



SUMMARY

I am a front-end developer with nearly 1 year of experience using Vue.js and knowledge of React and Spring Boot. I am passionate about programming and want to make a living from it. I am eager to learn and know how to research documentation.

CONTACT INFO

• 20/1 Tan Khai Street, Wards 4, Tan Binh District, Ho Chi Minh City

**** 0938865826

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, Vue JS, ReactJS, Java, Spring Boot, MySQL, git, Figma, Fluent in English

EDUCATIONS

BACHELOR OF MARINE DIESEL ENGINEER
HCM CITY UNIVERSITY OF TRANSPORT

09/2005 - 10/2009

CERTIFICATES

ADVANCED DIPLOMA IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

ApTech Computer Education

06/2023 - NOW

EXPERIENCES

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

07/2022 - 01/2023

LTV Software Co., Ltd

- Participate in developing the front-end and maintaining projects at the company.

INTERN FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

05/2022 - 07/2022

LTV Software Co., Ltd

- Work together with the team to build a Material Template Project using VueJS.
- Write a usage guide for project using Markdown and VueJS.
- Technologies used: HTML, SCSS, Tailwind CSS, VueJS 3, Element Plus.
- My responsibilities: Development, Bug fixing.
- Deployment Link for project: https://argon-dashboard-vue3.web.app.
- Deployment link for document: https://argon-dashboard-vue3-docs.firebaseapp.com.

DIGITAL MARKETING SENIOR SPECIALIST

06/2018 - 12/2019

MOA Viêt Nam

- Develop long- and short-term SEO and Social (Face Book Ads) strategies.
- Oversee or manage pay-per-click (PPC) campaigns with search engine marketing (SEM) strategists.
- Collaborate and oversee to produce compelling and high-quality website content, including blog posts, page descriptions, subwebsite.
- Work closely with Web master and IT team to employ customer experience and conversion rate optimisation methods to turn visitors into more active users/lead and to help improve website performance.
- Collaborate with others within the marketing department (as

The program starts in January 2021 and ends in June 2023, which consists of 4 semesters:

- Building a website with basic features.
- Building a PC game/app.
- Building software used in small and large businesses.
- Building a website and some mobile applications.

- social media team, PR) to align and manage SEO strategy, content website and other digital channels.
- Analyzes campaign performance and recommends solutions for performance optimization daily.
- Track key performance indicators (KPIs) weekly, report rankings, and recommend tactics to optimize.
- Company Link: https://moavn.com/

MARINE DIESEL ENGINEER

10/2009 - 06/2013

Working Over Sea On Motor Vessels

- After graduating from the Maritime University, I worked for Vietnamese state-owned shipping companies including Falcon Shipping and PVTrans Shipping as a Marine Engineer.
- My responsibilities included operating and repairing various systems such as the electrical control system, oil filtration system, and power generation system.
- In 2013, I resigned from my job in the maritime industry to work on land and take care of my parents, as I am their only child.

AWARDS & HONORS

SUCCESSFUL PROJECT DEVELOPMENT

10/2018

MOA Việt Nam

Successfully developing an online marketing service team and providing highly competitive service packages.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

BOOK STORE WITH REACT AND SPRINGBOOT

05/2023 - NOW

- To review the Spring Boot and React knowledge learned in school, I am currently trying to build a website for selling books. This project using Spring Boot for the backend and React for the frontend.
- Github: https://github.com/Trung-Hieu-Dev/fullstack-react-and-springboot

View details ☐

VUE 3 MUSIC APP

04/2023 - NOW

- Develop a music streaming website using Vue.js to practice and further improve my skills: VueJS 3, Pinia, Axios, Firebase, veevalidate, vue-i18n, vue-router....
- The functions include: adding, deleting, editing MP3 files, listening to music, login, logout, validation, post comments.
- Deployment link: https://music-store-kappa.vercel.app.
- Github: https://github.com/Trung-Hieu-Dev/vue-music-app

View details ☐

